Today is the first day
of Sabre's new project
to develop a chain
of retail stores.
I am meeting my new boss, Nellie
Bertram, Head of Special Projects.
Work starts at 9:00.
Sabre HQ is 30 minutes away
driving the speed limit,
giving everyone 20
minutes to shower,
plus 50 for Jim
to style his hair,
20 for breakfast, 40 for Erin to get
lost between her room and the lobby,
90 for Ryan to do
his morning ecstasy.
We're already 20 minutes late.
Wake up!
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, wake up! Ow!
Why are you sleeping
that way?
Oh. I was reading the mattress
tag and I fell asleep.
Stanley! Wake up! You've got to wake up!
The hotel's on fire!
Stanley, wake up!
It's pretzel day!
Good morning.
Hey, wake up. Let's have some fun.
We're in Florida now.
Hey, you. I'm so
glad this is happening.
I actually came to your
door twice last night.
Come on in,
the water's fine.
Oh, not cool!
I am on the two-kids sleep schedule,
so I'm up and at 'em at 4:15.
But no kids, so I honestly didn't
know what to do with myself.
And then I thought
of something. Uh...
Here is Dwight...
What the...
Oh, man.
What do you think happened?
Looks like Jim got mixed up
with some bad apples.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It wasn't me.
I got to find "Luwanda
at the Alcohol Club."
Puppet
Cool. For your kids?
Yeah. It's weird being away from them.
I've never done this before.
Attention, Dunder Mifflin
group, proceed outside.
The vehicle is waiting.
Seats have been assigned.
Shotgun goes to Ryan.
Congratulations, Ryan.
I need to make Nellie
see me as a leader today.
First impressions
get locked in forever.
When I first met Pam,
she said something
that slightly
rubbed me the wrong way.
Since then I've
loved working with Pam,
and she's frankly wonderful,
but I hate her.
I'll have
a bottle of the antacid.
Also I want to get
a souvenir for my son,
but his mother doesn't
acknowledge my paternity.
Do you have anything for that?
Also I want it to
have a Florida feel.
What does he like?
Power.
Okay, and this one is, "Huh. Don't
see too many museums around here."
Okay, Twiggy, that's enough.
Get in the car.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine, okay?
I'm just stressed
because I care
about this project.
And frankly,
the fact that none of you
are vomiting or
diarrheal right now,
I find very alarming.
Who says none of
us are diarrheal?
Are you sure it's stress?
Because I did poison you.
Very funny, Jim.
Oh, no, I'm serious.
I was thinking for this trip,
I have to do something epic,
so what should that be?
And then I thought of it.
I'll poison you.
What are you going to do? Are you
going to steal my newspaper,
or put a cricket in my cereal,
or something?
I'm gonna set your face on fire.
That's a good one.
Whoa. Stanley,
did you just come back
from burning down
a rival night club?
Laugh it up, Halpert.
I'm in Florida for a month without
my family, I'm going to enjoy this.
Want to get in?
You can work the iPod.
Yes.
You're a nice guy, Jim, but you
have no idea how to vacation.
Find some Kenny Loggins.
Loggins and Messina.
Did I say Messina?
Sorry, I couldn't resist.
It's so quiet.
I like it.
It's so peaceful, I've already
written 12 plays today.
It's so quiet, one might say
you could hear a pin...
I thought that
would be cooler.
I loved it.
Hey, can you pick up
the pin?
Some of us like to
work in our bare feet.
Of course. I will pick up the pin.
It is right here.
Got it. Can we see that?
Did you really find it?
Yes. Right here.
Got it. Dink. Ow.
In the trash.
Hey, why is it so quiet?
Shouldn't
the phone be ringing?
Uh-oh.
Erin set
the phone to voice-mail.
Great.
Oh, my God, we're screwed.
There.
Oh, there we go. Pam?
Yeah.
Can you get the phone?
Well, I'm not
the receptionist.
Well, you used to be.
I know, but I can't cover reception.
I have a ton of work to do.
Phone's ringing.
Will one of you get the phone? I am freaking out!
I know it's for me.
Are you guys kidding me? Stop
flirting and someone get the phone!
Answer the phone!
Pick up the phone!
Andy, you're standing up!
You're the closest one to it.
Fine.
Hello. Dunder Mifflin.
Hello, you've reached Dunder Mifflin.
How may I be of service?
How was the drive?
Fantastic.
Stanley drives so fast.
Life is short. Drive fast, leave a sexy corpse.
That's one of my mottos.
I would love to
hear the other mottos.
Quick query, Halpert.
No way.
Still queer?
Packer
You can't put me down.
Too strong.
Yeah, Dwight and Jim
tried to get me fired.
But I landed on my
feet down here in Florida.
You see, this cat's got nine
lives and a nine-inch...
Say, "So who's
leading this thing anyway?"
So who's leading
this thing anyway?
Psst. Say,
"I can't wait to meet him."
I can't wait to meet him.
"Him," you said? Don't think
a woman can be a leader?
I...
You poor, simple boy.
Expected a man, did you?
Strong, powerful, huge whopping penis?
Well, sorry to disappoint.
But my huge whopping penis is right
here, and I'm not afraid to use it.
So stop looking at my breasts,
and start looking at my penis.
I'm Nellie Bertram,
President of Special Projects.
In the next few weeks
we're going to throw
everything you
know about business
out of the window
and do it our own way.
Are your minds blown?
So, how did this special
project come about anyway?
Well, I interviewed to be
the manager of your branch.
After you decided I
wasn't a good fit...
It was...
Ah. Mmm-mmm.
It was. I went
on a shopping spree.
Very destructive,
I bought 13 pianos.
Then I realized, what if
Sabre had a store? Hmm?
So I called Jo, old friend,
founder of Sabre, and I told her,
and she grabbed me by the
shoulders and she said, "Yes!"
So let's talk about
this Sabre store then.
Probably going to
look stupid, right?
Like a big turd with a door
on the front, right?
What do you think
it should look like?
It might be fun if each store
had a different theme,
like a beach one,
a winter one, a jungle one.
No. Not a big fan of
the winter aesthetic.
Well, that was just one idea.
It doesn't have to be winter.
Oh, no, it does. It does.
It has to be winter,
and I reject it.
So I drew up a design concept,
probably going to be rubbish, right?
Would you like to look at it?
Just so you can laugh at it.
Yeah.
Let me just get
the projector working.
You got to stop with the antacids.
It's not the antidote.
You didn't poison me.
It's just stress.
Okay.
What is the antidote?
True love's kiss.
Jim, help me
lower this screen.
You're a big tall man.
You'd be hilarious trying to
do it, like a little boy.
Just let go of his balloon.
I'll do it.
I always say if you want something
done right, ask Dwight.
Right, Dwight.
Right, Dwight. Right, Dwight.
Sorry. Now you'll never be able
to get that out of your head.
I can do it.
There we go.
Yes, a complete inability
to pass gas, pervert.
Yeah, it's tender, but it can't be appendicitis.
I eat more than enough bacon.
Okay, what poison mimics the
symptoms of appendicitis?
You don't know. Hold on.
What kind of
poison did you use?
Dwight, I didn't poison you.
I was kidding.
Yeah, I'm going to
need an ambulance.
Hold on. I have the address
in my phone. Hold on.
Sabre has assigned...
Hold on one second.
...the following positions
in the retail division.
Uh, quick question.
Vice President, who is that?
There is no name listed.
Is there not? Maybe I'm just
waiting for someone to wow me.
Sir? Sir, where should
we send the ambulance?
Send it to
the freaking moon, idiot.
I'll tell you what, though,
since my move down to Florida,
I've really gotten back
into hunting, big-time.
- Hunting's so primal, almost sexual.
- Totally.
Yeah, I mean,
I'd never bang an animal.
You can hardly
tell the difference
between a boy or a girl,
you know?
But hunting's intense.
You talking about hunting?
I love hunting.
I'm a master hunter.
Did you say "masturbator"?
I'm a decent batter. My cousin,
Mose, that's a master batter.
Why are you
sitting down like that?
Why is everyone
else standing up?
Okay, team, let's get back to work!
Break's over.
Wow. Are you that bored?
It's just rum.
I'm not bored. I'm a pirate.
Is that another motto?
It's whatever you want.
Hmm.
Or do you only
drink with your kids?
No, let's do it.
Woah. That's healthy.
I've spent so much of
my life telling myself,
"Please, don't
end up like Stanley."
And now I'm wondering
if I even have what it takes.
We have the Sabre pyramid, right?
We've got a bunch of humans.
You guys. Humans, pyramid.
Human pyramid. Do you follow?
It's a team-building exercise.
You love it. Who's in?
Tallahassee, let's go.
Jim, are you in?
Oh, I don't know.
Sounds like a hoot. I'm in.
All right.
What the heck? Let's do it.
This is great.
This is going to be great.
I feel like I'm
in ancient Egypt.
I'll be on top. That's the
most important position.
Dude, I think you have appendicitis.
Dwight,
why don't we just hold off
with the human
pyramids for a while?
Everyone stop moving.
Everyone stop wiggling.
I feel like I'm
going to vomit.
Dude, don't you yak on me.
This shirt is Van Heusen.
Oh, stop moving.
No one's moving.
Arrest Jim.
He poisoned me.
What? No. No.
It was not a poisoning.
The one thing Pam
made sure I knew,
Florida's pretty loose
with the death penalty.
You need an operation.
You have appendicitis.
Oh! Who called it?
Nothing but net.
How long will he be gone?
Two or three days.
Don't remember me like this.
Remember me as the man
who pulled down the screen.
Drama queen, am I right?
Philip, if you're
hearing this memo,
that can only mean
one thing, I am dead.
You are the rightful heir to Schrute Farms.
Please, you must do one thing.
Kill Mose before he kills you.
Mose. Hey, it's Dwight.
Listen, yeah, I just want
to give you a heads up.
That was
an interesting diversion.
Should we get
back to the meeting?
Woah. Are those mini pizzas?
Yeah. I figure if
we keep things savory
while Oscar's mouth
is in canker country...
I also have some
bacon-wrapped dates on deck.
Look at these little mini pizzas.
Does this make me look huge?
Hey, guys,
look at me, I'm huge.
Hey, Darryl, good news,
your fax went through.
On  yeah.
UP high.
Yes, sir. Thanks.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Andy. I put
out some new magazines. Check it out.
Ah, Dwell.
I'm acting like I like
Reception, and I'm a really good actor
so people are actually buying
that I actually like Reception.
But I mean,
seriously, Reception sucks.
Ooh! There's the phone!
I just
got out of surgery.
What's going on? Fill me in.
Well, we broke into groups and the
groups are giving presentations later.
Who's doing the presentations?
Packer's giving one.
Jim will probably
give ours, I guess.
Damn it!
Let's see.
What else have you missed?
Ryan switched his
nametag to his pants,
so now it's like
if you wear yours
on your shirt,
you're a total dip.
But if you switch,
you're a copycat.
But I think I
figured out a solution.
What else? My shoes are...
...features the tech support area.
Bring in your product,
a bunch of nerdy
virgins fix it on the spot.
Huge for building loyalty.
Yes, that is
a very good point.
Yeah, Todd, decent idea.
Obvious, but interesting.
Dwight, are you all right?
I'm great. How are you?
Uh...
What's our presentation about?
Dwight, will you go
back to the hospital?
You were there for
like three hours.
I got the surgery.
What else is there to do?
Do 100 jumping jacks.
No. I don't feel like it.
You do 100 jumping jacks.
I don't feel like it either.
...ninety-seven, 98, 99...
I want the Vice Presidency.
You haven't done
any of the research.
You're too slow. You're too small.
Seabiscuit is a stupid name.
You guys sound just like
the enemies of Seabiscuit.
I'm going to do it.
Oh, let him do it.
Stanley,
are you listening to music?
Yep.
All right, who's ready
for the next presentation?
Oh... What is your topic?
What is our topic? Oh, what
a topic it is. Mmm-hmm.
Retail consumer habits.
Really? Okay.
Retail consumer habits is...
The only thing
you need to know
about retail
consumer habits is that
consumers are
mindless lemmings.
They just want to
be told what to do.
Fast-forward to today, and the
retail consumer is independent,
well-informed, super smart.
Super smart.
Okay.
Shopping habits are both
seasonal and cyclical.
What does this mean?
I can field this one.
No, sit down.
Seasonal, well, the Christmas shopping
season is certainly a busy one.
Back to school is as well,
and in early summer
it seems to slow down a bit.
But shopping is also cyclical.
The menstrual cycle determines
every choice a woman makes.
You see, during ovulation, a woman's
only goal is to get pregnant.
During menses, she is sad
that she has failed.
And how does
the woman console herself?
Shopping. Shopping.
Just, Jim, could you fetch me
some ice chips?
Thank you. Just gonna take a
brief pause at this point.
Thank you.
Oh, God.
Next slide.
Mail call!
His name is Oscar,
and he's got some mail
And he better open it or go to
jail, 'cause it's your taxes
His name is Kevin,
and no mail for him
But he got a coupon
for some frozen yogurt
Are those the lyrics?
"Anderson's Three Pillars
of Retail."
Crucial. So important.
Next.
Are there any questions?
What are the Three
Pillars of Retail?
Convenience.
Ingredients.
Service.
Burgers.
Building loyalty.
Killing royalty.
But truth be told,
we should really
disregard
Anderson's Three Pillars.
He was later
diagnosed with dementia.
You know what is important?
Is Dwight's pillars,
and there's only one, desire.
Do we have a desire
to dominate the retail space?
Not just succeed in it
but to dominate.
And looking around this room,
I'm not so sure that we do.
But we can get there.
And I can lead us there,
and that is all that matters.
Very true. Where there's
a will, there's a way.
I once spent
a passionate night
with Hugh Grant's brother,
John Grant.
He's older than Hugh,
just a little bit uglier.
How did I pull that off?
Sheer force of will.
That is very good, Dwight.
Thank you very much.
Any other questions?
Jim.
You are bleeding
through your shirt.
Oops.
That's embarrassing.
Egg on my face.
Ah...
Hey, having fun?
Yes, I am,
as a matter of fact.
Oh, I know how it is.
I know it's a lot of fun.
I don't know how it is.
Andy, this is a lame job.
What are you doing here?
I found my calling.
Andy, when I was 12 years old, we did
a field trip, a lock-in at the zoo.
I met this girl. I thought she was so perfect.
I was in love with her.
But when the sun came up,
I knew it wasn't real
because she was ugly
and I had grown tired of her.
I know you want
Reception today,
but tomorrow you
won't want to do her.
She's a dog.
Guys, I don't
like this analogy.
Oh, fine.
Did you see this?
It's nice.
I mean...
How are you feeling?
Amazing.
Just lost four
ounces of appendix,
already replaced
it with muscle.
Can I see the wound?
Oh, that's disgusting.
That's barely healed.
You're not paying me to heal.
You're paying me to kick ass.
A few hours ago, your body
was open like a cabinet.
That's right.
That is amazing.
Todd, look at that.
Ch, yikes!
Incoming.
Not so fast.
Would you come
in early tomorrow,
so we could talk about the
store over breakfast?
I feel you have
a lot to offer.
It would be an honor, ma'am.
I'll go ahead and cancel
my post-op checkup right now.
I had two goals today,
the first was to make myself the
clear candidate for Vice President.
I achieved that,
no thanks to my appendix.
The second was to find a
memorable souvenir for Philip.
For that, I do have
to thank my appendix.
Dunder Mifflin, how can I
help you save money on paper?
This is Andrew.
Hi, Andrew.
What happened to Erin?
Oh, she's on an assignment in
Florida for a couple weeks.
Oh, good for her.
She's such a sweetheart.
You tell her Donna
Moraski misses her.
I miss her, too.
Everyone, we have
a very special guest.
He turned an idea into a store,
into hundreds of stores.
I give you Wally Amos, founder
of Famous Amos cookies.
Yeah!
So I hear
you're all looking to
bake up some dough
in the sales game.
Well, back when I
was regular Amos...
What's under the cloth?
We'll get to that.
Cookies. I bet you
anything it's cookies.
It's cookies.
Let me finish my speech first.
Oh, we get the gist. It's just
success and effort, isn't it?
So just don't be coy.
Make with the cookies.
Cookies.
Famous, hi.
I'm sure you get ideas
for new cookies all the time.
But I...
Is it oatmeal with no raisins?
I'm sorry to have
wasted your time.
That's okay.
Thank you very much.